womensappeal.com 2008-04-08

# Privacy Policy of Women's Appeal Directory

|    

|    
** 1\.  **PRIVACY POLICY WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY**   
2\.  **SECURE SITE**  
3\.  **ORDER**  
4\.  **COOKIES**  
5\.  **LOG FILES**  
6\.  **SHARING**  
7\.  **LINKS**  
8\.  **NEWSLETTER**  
9\.  **SURVEYS & CONTESTS **  
10\.  **TELL-A-FRIEND**  
11\.  **SECURITY**  
12\.  **OPT-OUT**  
13\.  **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
**  
**1\. PRIVACY POLICY WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY**  

* * *

This Privacy Statement is effective for all users of WOMENSAPPEAL.COM ("WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY" or "our") and our related websites, including Customers, Affiliates and Newsletter Subscribers ("Users"). If you are not at least 18 years old you may not use the Site without adult supervision. You warrant that you are at least 18 years old or have obtained parental permission to use this Site. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to provide you with WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY's information collection practices (including the information WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY collects, how it is collected, and the circumstances under which the information is disclosed), and to demonstrate WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY's firm commitment to privacy and adherence to the California Online Privacy Protection Act. The following discloses the privacy practices for our website: [www.womensappeal.com](http://www.womensappeal.com/)  
**Return to Index.**

**2\. SECURE SITE**  

* * *

Our site uses an online secure order form. When a User's order is placed through our secure online server, or a User sends WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY an email, WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY collects confidential customer information. When a User sends an email (as distinguished from a secure order form, which is encrypted), it is not necessarily secure and is not encrypted. Information collected from affiliates and newsletter subscribers may not be encrypted or maintained on a secured site. All of the customer data WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY collects is protected against unauthorized access.   
**Return to Index.**

**3\. ORDER**  

* * *

WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY requests information from the User on an order form. The information that is collected to process the order may include contact information (name, shipping address, telephone number, fax number and/or email address) and financial information (credit card number, name on account, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers' orders. This contact information is used to contact the User.   
**Return to Index.**

**4\. COOKIES**  

* * *

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the User. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the User closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the User would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY has no access to or control over business partners' cookies.   
**Return to Index.**

**5\. LOG FILES**  

* * *

WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.   
**Return to Index.**

**6\. SHARING**  

* * *

WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY may share aggregated demographic information with WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY's partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY may use several credit card processing companies and banks to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY may share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY may release account information when WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY believes, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, prevent fraud, enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or to otherwise protect the rights, property and safety of WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY, our customers or other third parties.   
**Return to Index.**

**7\. LINKS**  

* * *

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY encourages its Users to be aware when they leave the WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. This Site may include links to other Internet sites, both related and unrelated to the Site, which may be of interest to users. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY may not have reviewed these sites and is not responsible for the content or availability of these sites. Descriptions of or references to products or publications not owned by WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY on this Site or any linked site do not imply any endorsement of such products or publications by WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY is not responsible for or liable for any damage, including damage caused by viruses, to your computer, computer system, or other property, during or on account of access or use of the Site or any sites to which the Site links.   
**Return to Index.**

**8\. NEWSLETTER**  

* * *

If a User wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.   
**Return to Index.**

**9\. SURVEYS& CONTESTS **  

* * *

From time-to-time WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY requests information from Users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the User therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.   
**Return to Index.**

**10\. TELL-A-FRIEND**  

* * *

If a User elects to use the WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY referral service for informing a friend about our site, WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY asks for the friend's name and email address. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY at [support@womensappeal.com](mailto:support@womensappeal.com) to request the removal of this information from their database.   
**Return to Index.**

**11\. SECURITY**  

* * *

This web site takes every precaution to protect Users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-Line. When the WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with encryption software. While WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY uses encryption to protect sensitive information online, WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY also uses its best efforts to protect user-information off-line. User information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. If you have any questions about the security at WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY, you can send an email to [support@womensappeal.com](mailto:support@womensappeal.com)  
**Return to Index.**

**12\. OPT-OUT**  

* * *

WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY Users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY's site at the point where WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY asks for information. For example, our order form has an opt-out mechanism so Users who do not wish to receive marketing material may keep their email address off of our lists. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [support@womensappeal.com](mailto:support@womensappeal.com)  
**Return to Index.**

**13\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  

* * *

If WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our Users are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY changes its privacy policy, WOMEN'S APPEAL DIRECTORY will notify users by way an update of this Policy.   
**Return to Index.**

| 

---|---|---
